Rivier Grullon

Santiago de los Caballeros, Santiago, Dominican Republic



grullonrivier@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/rivier-grullon-ba0a25204

Summary

Passionate about open source world, Innovation and Technology, being worked for different projects that help me to adopt to the changes quickly and made me a mature team worker. I'am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative

Experience



🦺 Software Developer

Intellisys D. Corp.

Oct 2020 - Present (1 year 6 months +)

Working on the voting system for the Dominican Republic Senate.

Technologies used:

Vue 2

C#

Umbraco

Firebase

Signal R

Boostrap

Migrating the system using:

Vue 3

Typescript

Signal R core

.NET 6

Jest

quasar

Sass



Open Source Developer

Crew Dev

Apr 2020 - Present (2 years +)



🕵 Internship

Intellisys D. Corp.

Nov 2020 - Mar 2021 (5 months)

Student Software Engineer

Cincinnatus Institute of Craftsmanship Aug 2019 - Oct 2020 (1 year 3 months)

Education

Dalita

Politecnico Salesiano Santo Domingo Savio

High School Diploma Aug 2013 - Jun 2019

cincinnatus institute of craftsmanship

web developer, Software developer 2020 - 2022

Skills

TypeScript • Vue.js • Node.js • Research • Web Development • PostgreSQL • MySQL • Databases • Git • REST APIs